[{"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Can it be normal for you and Jaycee?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Pretty awesome.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "How's she?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "I think a lot of it depends -- is dependent upon Jaycee and her attitude.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "So how easy is it to just say, OK, we're going to rebuild and get on with our lives?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Can you remember that feeling?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "It was -- I had a really hard time accepting it.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "I mean, like it was yesterday?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "I -- the hate fuels the fire for the changes that need to be made.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Has your feeling subsided at all or do you feel this awful hate towards them?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Well, it was not only the last thing that Jaycee touched that was her reality back then but it's also a symbol of new beginnings.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "And the significance of that is what?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "How do you hear?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "I kind of blew it off because I had heard it so many times.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "And what was your first thought when you -- when they did that?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "She knew.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "She knew?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "She needed it to come from them.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "But she wouldn't tell you?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "So you called the sheriff?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "I -- no, I -- no.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "I mean, you're sensing it's good news now?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Do you remember?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Too excited.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "You were too excited?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Same, same.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "What did her voice sound like after all that time?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Could you -- could you quite believe it?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Was it like some strange fairytale ending to the nightmare?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "All kinds.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What emotions did you go through?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "I have to.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Can you block it out completely?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "It is the understatement of the year.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Understatement, right?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, I think guilt is your word.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "How do you tackle that kind of emotional dilemma?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I think it's been extremely important that the media has respected -- thanks to the fabulous PR person, has respected their space.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "How are they dealing with the reality of discovery of the whole thing?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Having a life.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What's been the thing that she realized other than just seeing you again that she missed the most?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Does she have ambition now?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Being able to hold her.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "What's been the best part of it for you?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Do you think she'll -- may meet a Mr. Right, get married, live a fairy tale life that you would imagine you wanted for your daughter?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I don't think -- she's had a normal relationship with a man at all.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Because she's 31 now?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "She worked through some material early on and that's where the horse work was tremendously useful with her was that some of the early difficult experiences she was able to get in touch with in the arena with the horses, with my assistant and the other therapist assistants and --", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Sort of awful flashbacks, nightmares?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "AILEY: It's actually so simple that it's hard to describe sometimes.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "When you bring in horses to somebody who loves animals, loves horses and so on, what's the concept for how that acts as therapy?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "You can look at this wonderful woman right here, and you can see where so much of Jaycee's strength comes from, in her poise, in her ability to stare things straight down.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "How vital is that do you think to what happened?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Sadness.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "I mean, how would you sum up your feelings?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "All of 2008, I was in Vegas along with Lavelle.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "What did you see?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Was he ready to go?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "To do 50 shows?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Did you ever see him taking drugs of any kind?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "-- Is this another Michael stunt?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "You saw that on CNN?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "I was at the Staples Center.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Where were you?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Did you see him much?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "So all this was sort of brand new to you?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Does it seem like a weird other world?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "So you're left with a terrible accident.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Why would he?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Have either of you ever heard him speak like that?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "We were going to do short films.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "What was he planning to do?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "The best.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "How good was Michael Jackson, as an entertainer?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Amazing.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "How good a singer was he?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "Top.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "And dance-wise, mesmerize?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I think he would like to be remembered as someone that was always, you know, making sure that what he delivered to his fans and to his audience was original.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "How do you think, finally, Michael would like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "I was going to agree with that and say that anything he wanted to do, he wanted it to be the best.", "docId": "111101pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Michael, you were going to say?", "qSentId": 716}]